Graphic / UX Designer. Frontend Developer

DARIA GERMASH

FULL TIME | REMOTE | PART TIME

Hello! I'm from Ukraine! Now live in Belgium.

I love design and programming as well as running and selfdevelopment, photography and learning new things. Please feel free to contact me or take a look at my experience and portfolio via link https://cv-daria-germash.netlify.app/designer_portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer, UX Designer, Front-end Developer at Mintus / OCMW Bruges (IT Department)

5th of June 2023 - up to now | Bruges. Belgium

Graphic Design, Brand Identity;

- Web Design, UX Design;
- Front-End Development;
- Design of printed production,
- Prepress/

Acomplishments

I've started working with PHP web-

- sites and keep learning PHP development using UDEMY Courses;
 - Graphic design (Development
- mock-ups for wide-format and multi-page printing production);
 - UX design (Developing mock-ups for
- company applications, sharepoint, wide-format and multi-page printing production);
 - Content managing and filling of php
- websites;
 - Identity (Development of new logo
- and brandbook for all brands of company);
- Collaboration and consulting with other departments in field of design and web-development;
- Strengthening of language skills
- (Dutch) and integration in flamish working flow.

Designer, Web Developer. Volunteering and Freelance

2015 - up to now | Ukraine / Belgium

- Graphic Design, Brand Identity;
- Web Design, UX Design, Front-End Development;
- Design / Redesign of printed production, Prepress;
- Photography

Graphic / UX Designer at XPG August 2016 - 2022 | Ukraine

- Graphic Design, Brand Identity;
- Web Design, UX Design, Front-End Development;
- Design / Redesign of printed production, Prepress.

Graphic Designer at AntForWeb August 2014 - 2022 | Ukraine

- Website design, UX Design, Graphic Design, Brand Identity;
- Front-End Development;
- Project support and content filling.

Marketing Manager at Technobud Ltd

August December 2006 - 2015 | Ukraine

- Marketing, Logistics;
- Managing advertisment, creating ideas for promotion production etc.
- Graphic design (developing mock-ups, prepress);
- Web Development and content filling.

PROJECTS / PORTFOLIO

Web Design & Development

working projects

https://celiac.org.ua https://xprogaming.com https://pgswork.com.ua



Front-End Development study projects

https://kekstagram https://cat-energy https://technomart

EDUCATION

Self-education in IT and UX Design

until now

HTML Academy (Online)

Front-End Development

May 2021 - February 2022 · September 2022 - November 2022

Computer Academy "STEP"

Graphic and Web Design **2012 - 2015 | Ukraine**

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Marketing

September 2000 - September 2005 | Ukraine

LANGUAGES

Native tongue

Ukrainian, Russian

SKILLS

- Graphics
- Illustration
- Photography & Retouch
- Prepress
- Digital printing
- Valid HTML5 and CSS3 (Adaptive design and it's layout);
- JavaScript: Web Interfaces
 Development (keep learning);
- PHP: Wordpress (keep learning);
- Preprocessing and Automation (keep learning);
- Version Control Git (keep learning)
- All regular PC Apps (e.g Microsoft Office) etc.

Commonly-Used languages

English **B2** Dutch **B1** (Keep learning)

SOFT SKILLS

I have a good skills in understanding clients and colleagues in field of tasks they want to give but couldn't find words to explane it clearly. My limited knowledge of Dutch is not a barrier for understanding tasks and opinion of those who give them, explaining my vision of resolving issues and usual chatting with colleagues.

Every day of my work experience on site in Mintus helps me to develop and improve my comunication skills, using the language I've started to learn a little bit more than year and half ago. Working flow in my team in contact with other divisions as well as external organizations helps me in selfdevelopment and understanding needs of colleagues, their expectations from my work, and provides getting qualified product as the result.